WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Go, go, go, go, go!
Suspect on foot, entering warehouse.
In pursuit.
Go, go!
Freeze! Stop right there!
Put down the weapon!
Can't stop it now.
- Nothing can stop it.
- On the ground!
On the ground. Drop it, right now!
Halloran! Detective Halloran!
If he's not here in 17 minutes,
five people are gonna die.
Get Halloran here, now!
Where the fuck is Halloran?
People are gonna die, man!
- Doesn't he know?
- All of you, get back.
- Halloran!
- Edgar!
Edgar, what the fuck are you doing?
- You put down that remote.
- I can't.
- What's that for?
- The games are just getting started.
- What game?
- His games, his rules.
I gotta choose who dies. Them or me.
Edgar, I don't want to shoot you,
but I will.
Drop the remote.
- I got him, should I take it?
- No, no, no. Target the remote.
If he moves to trigger it,
blow it to shit.
Running out of time!
- Who else is there?
- Edgar! Tell us what's going on!
- Who's controlling you?
- I'm not fucking dying.
Which one of you assholes
shot him in the chest?
The game.
It's started...
What is this?
- What the hell?
- What the fuck?
Yo, what the hell?
- Oh, shit.
- Oh, God.
What's going on?
No, no, no, no.
Help me!
No, no, no.
- Help!
- Somebody please help me.
Please, help me!
Help! Help!
Just stay the fuck back!
I'm sure you're all
wondering why you're here.
You deny culpability, no doubt,
for the circumstances
in which you find yourselves.
Salvation can be yours,
if you cleanse yourselves
of the habitual lies
which have brought you here.
Lies that you have told yourselves.
Lies that have brutalized others.
Confess. The truth will set you free.
But any attempt to violate
my rules will kill you.
I want to play a game.
Fuck you!
First, an offering of blood,
no matter how little,
will give you a green light
to escape from this room with your lives.
If you can release yourself
from your demons,
you can begin to shed the chains
that those demons bring with them.
Make the simple blood sacrifice
that I've requested
or face severe consequences.
The choice is yours.
The fuck's going on over here?
- No, no, no...
- No, no, no!
No!
No! No!
What do we do? What do we do?
Someone do something!
Hey! Wake up!
Wake up!
Stop!
"An offering of blood."
"No matter how little."
Cut yourself! You need to cut yourself!
He wants blood, and then you're free!
Cut yourself, he wants blood!
Cut yourself!
Fuck!
Come on, come on, come on.
Yes! Holy shit!
You need to cut yourself!
- Get off me!
- You need to cut yourself!
What the...
No.
Cut yourself! You need to cut yourself!
Cut yourself!
Where the fuck are we?
He hit the remote,
but nothing triggered.
As far as we know.
You think the game's real?
Don't know.
Why do you think he asked for you?
We're good friends.
I put him away twice.
Edgar Munsen is a sociopathic meth head.
Been in and out of prison
for assault and battery,
armed robbery, drug dealing.
Nice guy.
Doc, we need him awake.
We've got questions.
Sorry, Detective.
The bullet's lodged against the heart.
I've got him in a barbiturate-induced coma
until he stabilizes.
- How long?
- Swelling has to come down first.
Two hours. Two weeks. Can't tell you.
Excuse me.
Start the suspect list
with Munsen's known associates.
This is not gonna end well.
Hungry?
Help!
Please, somebody help us!
Please! Don't--
Stay still.
What do you want with us?
That voice...
It said salvation can be ours
if we cleanse our soul of our lies.
Is this some kind of
fucked up confessional?
The truth will set us free.
Honey, my soul is clean.
It's Anna.
And bullshit.
I'm Mitch.
What's your name?
Carly.
Don't touch me!
This is some bastard's
sick idea of a joke?
He said it was a game.
Well, then I hope, for all of our sakes,
that it is a game.
Oh, yeah? Why is that, sweetheart?
Because games can be won.
This is crazy.
- What the hell?
- Did anyone phone the police?
Yeah.
Underhand!
- Whoa!
- Overhand!
Okay, you got some heat on it!
Cell phone's off for a reason, Halloran.
Well, what do you think, El?
I don't know.
He looks a little "pail."
Let's get this thing off.
- Ooh.
- Ah.
Hmm.
Hm!
Someone's been studying up
on John Kramer.
Copycat?
Hope not.
Kramer's been dead for ten years.
- Keith!
- What's up, Doc?
- Hey, man, how you doing?
- I'm good.
- Good to see you.
- You too, man.
- You're working this neighborhood now?
- Uh, yeah, I joined homicide last month.
Jesus. What happened to this guy?
You two know each other?
- Logan was our medic in Fallujah.
- Mm.
Hey, uh, I'm sorry to hear
about Christine.
How you been, man?
Uh, good, Keith.
Yeah, I'm doing well.
All right.
Eleanor.
What is it?
Okay, then.
"And then there were four..."
You got a computer we could stick that in?
The games have begun again.
And they will not stop
until the sins against
the innocent are atoned for.
I will take care of the next four.
You take care of the rest.
We gotta get that to voice rec.
It's not him.
Can't be.
Right?
AW, shit.
What the fuck?
No, that's not creepy at all.
No. No!
No, no, no...
Ah, shit!
Help!
Somebody please help us!
Where is this sick fuck taking us?
Did anyone see anything?
No, nothing. I got fucking drugged!
He said, "Confess"! We have to confess!
Yeah, you got something you wanna confess?
Have at it. Come on!
Man, we all have something to confess!
I sold a kid a bike once.
He had an accident ten minutes
after I sold it to him.
It's not my fault he couldn't handle
such a powerful damn bike, all right?
- He died!
- That's it?
That's all you did?
You sold a kid a bike he died on?
- Come on, man!
- That's it! I said that's it, man!
Yeah, bullshit.
What about you, sweetheart? Come on!
We lost our baby.
Anna... Anna.
Tell me that this isn't happening.
My husband made a mistake.
No, no, no.
That's not a confession, come on, come on!
I don't know what the fuck
you want me to say, okay?
I let our marriage fall apart.
No, no. A confession is,
"I killed a hooker in Tulsa,"
or, "I ate my fucking neighbor."
Not, "I need marriage counseling."
- Carly?
- No, nothing I can think of!
- Yeah, well, think faster!
- You think faster!
Oh, my God.
We're gonna hang.
Play the damn tape, Mitch.
Oh, God!
While I am certain that there is a desire
to point fingers at me
for the blood that has been shed,
unless you turn that finger inward,
I assure you, more blood will be lost
and all will be judged.
We will begin with one.
One who is not only a liar,
- but a thief.
- Hey!
A purse-snatcher.
And when you had a chance
to fix the harm that you'd done,
you chose to do nothing.
Now it is you who could die
without the right medication.
While unconscious,
this deceiver among you,
this criminal, was injected with a poison.
One of the syringes in front of you
holds the antidote.
One is a saline solution.
The other, an acid that will cause
an excruciating death.
Inject the correct one
and your chains will be released.
Failure to make the right choice
could result in death for you all.
I ask you, what is a life worth to you?
One of you 'fess up, or we all die.
- Okay, check yourself for marks.
- Huh?
If he injected us, there could be marks.
Bingo.
- What are you doing?
- It's okay. It's okay.
You just gotta pick a needle, Blondie.
Look, we get out of these things
when you pick an antidote.
Or else we all die, Carly!
No. What if it's the acid?
- I won't.
- Bullshit, you won't.
Maybe just confess, Carly.
Okay, did you steal purses?
Yeah, years ago, but...
- I didn't kill anyone!
- No, no, no!
No, that's not the repentant attitude
this guy's looking for, okay?
You're lying! You're lying!
No! I was broke, okay?
And yes, somebody died,
but it wasn't my fault.
Okay. Choose.
- Or I'm gonna stick them all into you!
- No!
- Yo, man!
- Are you kidding me?
- Stop!
- Just let her look!
Do any of these numbers
mean anything to you?
- Choose now!
- I'm trying!
Three dollars and 53 cents.
What? What does that mean?
- What?
- What a life is worth to me.
Oh, fuck.
Choose, right now! Come on, pick!
- Pick one! Pick now! Please!
- I can't do it!
- Pick one now!
- We're all going to die!
- Come on.
- Pick now! Choose!
Come on, Carly!
I'm not gonna fucking do it!
No, I'm not going to!
- Fuck you! I won't do it.
- Pick one, now!
Come on, pick! Pick!
Fuck! I'm not gonna pick!
- Come on!
- Now! Now, Carly, now!
Pick now!
Pick one!
- Fucking asshole!
- Hey! Hey!
I'm not the one who put us here.
Get a hold of yourself.
I just saved our lives.
Yeah, but you took hers. You killed her.
- You selfish son of a bitch!
- Stop! Both y'all need to chill!
What the hell?
"A life is Worth $3.53."
- What?
- That's what she said.
Yeah.
Three dollars and 53 cents.
There's more numbers
on the inside of this.
It could be the combination.
Dental IDs Buckethead as Malcolm Neale.
Malcolm Neale? I remember that case.
His wife was murdered five years ago.
A home invasion. Perp slit her throat.
- He made him watch.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, I remember.
Malcolm Neale was a, uh,
degenerate gambler.
Wife's murder was on him.
He owed some bad guys some money.
And did you ever get around
to convicting those bad guys?
Scratch marks from fingernails.
There was a struggle,
presumably with the killer.
The partial decapitation
was made by a circular saw.
There are traces of ferric oxide,
hematite, in the wound.
- Rust from blades.
- Okay.
What about the voice recording?
Anything off the flash drive?
The voice was John Kramer. Matched.
- Identical.
- Matched?
- What, he came back from the dead?
- Wouldn't be his first time.
Just because someone is dead
doesn't mean they can't have a voice.
Give us enough time,
we speak for the dead.
On the roof, Edgar Munsen was
spouting off about starting a game.
The recording says there are
four more potential victims.
Four people fighting for their lives.
God...
Okay, we're in the countryside somewhere.
I can't make out any landmarks, nothing.
Oh, God. Who's doing this to us?
I have no idea.
What's your name?
Ryan.
And what's your sin, Ryan?
Sold bad mortgages, sold good coke,
cheated on my taxes, cheated on my wife.
Both of them.
So, you know...
Nothing that bad.
What's your story, lollipop?
It was my husband's fault.
Oh, come on. Bullshit.
Why... Why am I being punished
for something that he did?
Huh?
If he hadn't fallen asleep,
he wouldn't have rolled over
and suffocated our baby.
It's not my fault.
No, no. No!
For real, you don't think
he's trying to tell us something?
Look, there are two perfectly
good doors right here.
Right, so we go through the door
that leads exactly he wants us to go?
- No, thanks.
- No, Mitch is right.
- I don't think this is--
- Back the fuck up.
Man, get that shit out of my face.
Oh, my God!
Help me! Help. Please.
Ah! What the fuck?
There's wires, there's something...
Help! Help!
See? See?
Looks like there's a bunch
of wires wrapped around his leg...
and around some pulleys.
Okay, there's, uh...
there's some kind of handle.
Guys, there's a tape.
It's tighter! It just got tighter!
- Oh, God!
- Okay.
- Oh, God! Oh!
- Okay, how do we get the tape?
- Go slow.
- Oh, yeah. Be careful.
- Really slow.
- Yeah, okay. Careful.
Careful. Careful. Careful.
Oh, please be careful.
Oh, God.
Careful, careful, careful...
Oh, God!
Oh, God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my-- You guys aren't helping!
Grab the tape! Grab the tape.
No way, man.
No, you gotta fucking grab the tape.
I saved your fucking life, Mitch!
Grab the tape!
- Just do it!
- Please.
Please, yeah. Yeah, come on.
Come on. Come on, man.
Oh, my God.
- You almost got it?
- I'm trying, dude!
You got it. You got it.
Okay. All good, all good.
You got it?
Oh, God, oh, good.
Play the tape, Mitch. Play the tape.
No, you play the tape, man.
There are no shortcuts in life.
Please forgive the rather crude example
I will make of your decision
to not follow the rules.
Pull the handle and you will be set free.
What does he mean "set free"?
Good luck, lollipop.
Oh, God.
Hey.
Prelim report on Buckethead.
It says the particles found
on the body are animal feces.
Cow, chicken, pig...
They also found traces
of Aujeszky's disease.
Aujeszky's disease?
It's a virus.
Mostly known because, when swine get it,
farmers have to wipe out
the entire sounder.
I'm impressed.
Keep digging-
Maybe I can track the virus to a location.
Dr. Nelson, another one, possible jumper.
Any identification on the victim?
No. Looks like the same killer.
This was on the body.
No link so far to any of our suspects.
- Is it Kramer? Do you know?
- Is this crime related to Jigsaw?
Think it's any coincidence that
Edgar Munsen happens to be a guest here?
I think it's highly unlikely
he woke up from a coma,
climbed on a roof, and threw a girl off.
But I did check with the ICU.
He's still there.
Looks like acid.
There's a depletion
of adenosine triphosphate
in the muscle fibers. Rigor mortis.
Clearly, she didn't die from the fall.
It's hydrofluoric acid.
Look, here. This is the injection point.
The vein carried it all the way
to the heart, where it's singed.
How do you know it was hydrofluoric acid?
Saw a lot of it in Fallujah.
Never injected, though.
A puzzle piece.
Jig-fucking-saw!
What's Logan's deal?
What happened in Fallujah?
Uh, he, uh...
- He got captured.
- Oh.
But not before taking out three Taliban.
Well from what I heard,
they tortured the shit out of him.
He spent months in the VA hospital
when he got back.
Think he snapped?
Come on, man,
you're talking about a brother.
I got a brother. He's a fucking asshole.
What do you think
about his second, Eleanor?
She's got a great ass, big mouth.
- Seems to get off on this sick shit.
- Yeah.
Motherfucker!
Shit. What the fuck?
Oh, fuck.
I'm a good person.
I'm a good person, I don't deserve this.
I confess...
I confess. I con--
I confess that this is fucked up!
What?
Hey, guys.
Hey, guys!
Somebody turned on the TV.
Hello?
Yeah, we got one, too.
- I'm gonna have to lift you.
- What?
We gotta get the remote.
Okay, fine.
Got it?
Got it!
No! No!
No!
In the past, you have all
put your own interests above others,
and then lied to yourselves,
and deceived the world
about your callousness,
your larceny, your criminality.
Now, you will look in the mirror
and you will face who you really are.
The choices you have made
may cost you your life.
You cannot escape the truth.
There is, however,
one person who can help you.
Ryan.
If he pulls the lever
before you are buried alive...
you will live.
Ryan, free yourself to free them.
Ryan.
Ryan?
No! No!
- What is that?
- It's grain!
- Ryan, man, we're gonna get buried alive!
- Ryan!
Ryan!
- Get to the handle!
- Ryan!
- I can't!
Please, Ryan!
Hurry, man!
Ryan!
You have to do it!
Oh, God!
Get to the handle!
Ryan, pull the fucking handle!
Please!
What's your story, sweetheart?
What are you asking, Detective?
You one of those, uh, kinky types?
Like a little pain?
Why?
You wanna get punished?
Too late.
Already got an ex-wife
that tortures me every day.
- Maybe you deserve it.
- Probably.
Where were you the night
Malcolm Neale got murdered?
Home.
- Alone.
- Cool.
Oh. Can you prove that?
Do I need to?
- Come home soon, Daddy.
- I will. I'm--
I'm sorry you have
to stay so late again, Judy.
Don't worry about it.
All right, sleep sweet, Mel.
I love you.
- Love you too, Daddy.
- Love you, bye.
Bye.
Logan.
How did you find Eleanor?
My assistant?
Is that all she is?
It's been two years since
Christine passed. It's just--
- I wouldn't blame you.
- Yes, but I'm a professional.
Uh, Logan, you ever heard
of a website called "Jigsaw Rules"?
No.
Buried deep online.
Took some digging,
but it's a site devoted to Jigsaw.
Half of it's bullshit, posers,
but there's some stuff on there...
...that is really messed up.
A lot of sick fucks.
Okay?
We did a darknet IP trawl.
Got a lot of hits from your assistant.
She's a regular.
Downloaded some shit you cannot imagine.
So you're saying that
Eleanor Bonneville is our copycat?
No, that's not what we're saying.
You check her alibi?
She said she was home the morning
Buckethead was found hanging in the park.
Uh, 7:00 a.m.? Home alone? Single woman?
- That does sound suspicious.
- All right, let's rewind.
How did Eleanor come to you?
She sought out the department
to do her residency.
And after that?
After she finished her residency?
I mean, three months ago,
she was offered a job
running the show
at the Cleveland city morgue.
Why didn't she take that?
Would you want to move to Cleveland?
That's the lab. Results are in.
Okay, so this is the DNA of the blood
scraped from under the fingernails
of the first victim, Malcolm Neale.
Yeah, Buckethead.
Can you ID it?
Already did.
This is a blood sample of a perp
taken a decade ago.
You might remember the case.
It's an exact match.
Whose blood is it?
John Kramer.
What?
That's impossible.
That's a fact.
The blood under the fingernails of
our first victim is John Kramer's blood.
The Jigsaw Killer.
Ryan!
Help!
- Ryan!
- Help!
Pull the lever!
Ryan!
Uh...
- Uh...
- Get to the handle!
Help, now!
Ryan!
No!
Go to hell!
You gotta help us now, man!
Help!
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck!
Ryan!
- Pull the handle, Ryan!
- Ryan!
Pull it!
Ryan!
We're gonna die in here! Please!
For the love of God, just pull it!
If we die, you die!
Oh, God...
Here's the GPS location
on Ms. Bonneville's cell.
Great.
Is Jigsaw dead?
Did Kramer die, or do we have proof?
What do you have to say to all
the panicked citizens who want answers?
Turned your phone off?
And yet here you are, you found me.
You'd make a good detective.
Or maybe I'm just too predictable.
Predictable? No.
Halloran's passing the blame around.
He's looking at us.
Yeah. They're watching my house.
Cause he thinks your alibi is shit.
You really love that guy, huh?
First year at County, clean case.
A predator by the name
of Alistair Schultz.
Halloran roughed him up
while he was in custody.
The lawyer used that to get him off.
The very next day,
he kills an eight-year-old girl
who shows up on my table.
The first of many.
Halloran...
can't help himself.
Can't get out of his own way.
So, no, I don't have
much love for the guy.
Well, it's a job, Logan.
You can't make it personal.
When you have a little girl one day...
Why didn't you tell me
about the job offer in Cleveland?
- You would've told me to take it.
- Yes. Yes, you're damn right I would.
- It's complicated.
- We are past complicated.
When Buckethead was strung up...
I wasn't at home like I told the cops.
I was at my, uh...
- ...studio.
- What studio?
Why couldn't you tell them that?
Like I said, it's...
It's complicated.
You don't think they're
gonna find out about it?
They know about the Jigsaw fan website,
whatever the fuck you're doing on that.
They're gonna find out about everything.
El, they think I'm involved.
Show me.
- Oh, Jesus!
- Okay...
- I should warn you, because...
- Can you turn the lights on?
Eleanor...
What is this?
Hey, a girl's gotta have a hobby.
A hobby?
Is that what you call it?
How about a stamp collection?
That's a hobby.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Supposedly,
John Kramer designed this trap
for a game that took place
before all the others.
They found the plans in his lab.
I built it myself.
Got them from some guy on the Internet.
Rumor is, not only did John design this...
...he built one.
Well, I'm sorry to disappoint,
but none of Kramer's victims
died in any device like this.
The wounds don't match the design.
Maybe the bodies were never found.
And maybe it never happened.
Maybe someone's playing games with you.
What are you doing with all this stuff?
You need to get rid of it now.
Great work.
Now we've got probable cause.
- You're not gonna believe this.
- What?
The commissioner wants
to see Jigsaw's remains.
Wants proof he's really dead.
- What?
- Yeah.
Said he wants to calm the peoples' fears.
Are you serious? Chasing a dead man.
This is election year bullshit.
That is all yours.
I'm gonna follow up on these.
Right on.
Halloran.
He's in a fucking coma,
how does he just disappear?
He's still breathing.
What is it?
It says my name.
You know what happens
if we don't follow the rules.
Hello, Mitch.
You've admitted to
selling a boy a motorcycle.
But you have not told
the entire story, have you?
Six hundred dollars for a bike
that you listed in excellent condition.
Even though you knew
the brakes were faulty.
You took his 600 bucks.
And in return,
you delivered him to his end.
He was my nephew,
and he never hurt anyone.
The device you see here
has a unique power source.
It's the same engine that graced
the bike you sold my nephew.
- Fuck.
- However, I assure you,
the brake lever
for this one works perfectly.
- Oh shit.
- Look, you're right, man!
Avoid the dangers around you,
hit the motorcycle brake handle,
- and the motor will stop.
- Oh, shit!
Live or die, Mitch.
The choice is yours.
Shit! No, no, no!
Oh, shit.
Look, I'm sorry! Stop, please!
I'm sorry about your nephew!
Anna, help!
Get the fuck up here!
I don't want to die!
Stop! Stop it!
Stop!
All right.
Anna, you gotta help me!
Hurry up! Hurry, please!
Please help! Hurry! Hurry!
I don't wanna die! I don't wanna die!
Mitch, pull the brake! Pull the brake!
Pull... pull the brake!
Anna, you did it!
You saved me!
Anna... Anna, get me out of here, please!
You did it! Anna, you did it!
No, no, no!
Edgar Munsen was in a coma.
You got one job!
One job to do, you useless mother--
Yeah.
Anything?
Nothing.
Pulled a Houdini. Nobody saw shit.
Just pulling Kramer's casket out now.
Reporters?
Yup.
Good.
End this nonsense once and for all.
John Kramer is dead
and has been for ten years.
Enough of this John Kramer bullshit.
- It's not him!
- Uh...
You may wanna rethink that.
Why? What's going on?
Let's just say you can
call off the hunt for Edgar Munsen.
Oh, come on!
Okay, get a warrant for Bonneville,
I'll see you there.
- Go, go, go.
- Move it! Move it!
Let's go.
Take the left.
Two on the right.
Go, go, go, go, go!
- Clear on the left!
- Clear!
- Watch your left.
- Eyes up!
Jesus!
Two left.
So, what, Bonneville just leaves a body
hanging in her studio?
- Come on, man.
- I know.
I'll go pick up Logan.
I'll get the girl.
Gonna need you to show me
those wrists, brother.
- I didn't do anything, Keith.
- Look, listen, listen.
I have photos of you.
Yeah, you and Eleanor
in your warehouse of torture devices.
- Wait, you were there?
- Yeah, I was there.
I just saw a third body that looks like
it's been through a meat grinder.
All right. Someone is trying to frame us.
- Tell me where Eleanor is.
- The studio I can explain.
- You just have to trust--
- You know where she is?
Keith! I'll tell you everything I know.
I know who did this.
And you do, too.
Who found the body at Eleanor's studio?
Jesus!
- Halloran.
- He had motive.
He wanted Edgar dead.
Who ordered the targeting of the remote?
If he moves to trigger it,
blow it to shit.
Go on.
Yeah, everybody targeted the trigger,
but did anyone actually see
what Halloran was aiming at?
He had no plan to let Edgar walk.
You think your partner knows
that you're with IA?
- So, I'm right.
- Jesus.
I've been onto Halloran
since before all of this started.
IA has him connected
to multiple homicides going back years.
Now these latest Jigsaw murders.
The three bodies we brought you,
we found they're all mixed up
in Halloran's cases.
Bring him in.
Halloran is trying to frame me.
- Don't even know what he's got against me.
- Really?
You know you called him out
for screwing up slam-dunk cases.
You said he was a moron
in the press twice.
No, I said he was an impulsive asshole...
twice.
You blame him for what happened
to Christine, don't you?
I don't know how to prove
Halloran's the copycat.
It's Halloran. It's him.
Let me help you build your case.
Let me get you proof.
Let me open up Edgar Munsen.
We match that slug to Halloran's gun.
- What kind of firearm do you use?
- Glock 22.
Most cops do.
Except Halloran. He's got a 17.
Nine by nineteen Parabellum.
That's a Glock 17.
Okay-
I'll take you home.
You stay there until I call you.
I'll get Halloran.
El, where the hell are you?
Call me, it's urgent.
Jesus!
El!
I've been trying to call you.
- I don't know how that body--
- No, no, no. It's okay.
They don't think it's you or me.
They have their sights set on Halloran.
I found it
I think I know where
the game is being played.
I found the farm.
That's great, let's call a detective.
No!
Halloran's behind this.
We can't trust the cops.
What?
You wanna see this game for yourself.
You get off on this shit?
Logan.
This is a chance for us to save lives.
So we're gonna take on a serial killer
with what, our cunning intellects?
And this.
Anna! Don't leave me!
Anna?
Anna!
I'm bleeding out, Anna!
Motherfucker!
Anna!
Okay-
Don't leave me, please!
Hello, Anna.
John?
John Kramer?
What's going on?
You're about to play a game.
Oh, no, no.
What are you doing, John?
What are you doing?
It's a final test.
I already passed your test!
Look at my fucking leg!
That wasn't your test, Ryan.
And that wouldn't have been necessary...
if you'd simply played by the rules.
But you don't like rules, do you?
You want me to show mercy?
You, who hasn't taken even
a single step toward confessing?
You, who is responsible
not for one death, but for three?
Your life of reckless deceit...
- Whoo! Yeah!
- ...started in high school.
- And only grew worse.
- Sit down!
- Sit the fuck down!
- Get the fuck off me!
You lied to the authorities
multiple times, Ryan,
pinning the blame solely on the driver,
your deceased best friend.
You know what you did to his family? Hm?
And you've only gotten worse
over the years.
I did it. Okay, I fucking did it.
I did it, but it was so long ago.
I wanna live.
- I wanna live.
- As do I, Ryan.
As do we all.
But things happen.
Were it not for a careless mistake
by a resident at the hospital I was in...
my cancer could have
been diagnosed a lot sooner.
It was simply the wrong name on an X-ray.
Would've saved me a whole lot of hardship.
And you, Anna.
I didn't do anything, John.
You know me!
Please don't do this to me.
We were neighbors, Anna and I.
My first chemo sessions were
very difficult, to say the least.
Anna and her husband, Matthew,
were so kind, so supportive.
I thank you for that.
Why are you doing this to me?
Those were better days
for you, weren't they, Anna?
But your poor husband, Matthew...
I know the two of you
didn't always get along.
But to have to endure that tragedy,
the death of a child, that's, uh...
one of life's greatest burdens, isn't it?
If only he hadn't
fallen asleep that night.
Then he wouldn't have rolled over
and, uh, suffocated your baby.
That is what happened, right, Anna?
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up. Shut up!
I mean, it's horrible, how horrible,
to have to live with such a thing.
It could make a person go mad,
couldn't it?
What are you gonna do to us?
Me?
I'm not gonna do anything.
You have to simply assume responsibility.
For who you are.
This is it.
How do you know this is it?
Tuck's Pig Farm.
It was shut down due to an outbreak
of Aujeszky's disease.
Buckethead's sample. The pig virus.
This farm was in Jill Tuck's family.
Jigsaw's wife.
Still is.
Although the place
was shuttered years ago.
Well, it looks like
somebody's here.
You sure you wanna do this?
Halloran, it's Hunt. Call me back.
We're at Halloran's house,
but he's not here.
- You got a location on him?
- Searching.
Sir?
Okay, we need to bring him in. Now!
Check this out.
That's a lot of blood.
What's to bet this is where
Buckethead was decapitated.
It's Jigsaw.
Jigsaw is dead.
Is he?
Please...
I'll do anything you want, John,
just please let me go.
Please.
Did you know that pigs are
highly compassionate animals?
They show distress
if they see any other animal,
including humans, suffering.
What about you, John?
Where is your compassion?
We all have a thumb on the scale, Anna.
For good or for evil.
You've been weighing in
on the wrong side of the scale.
Both of you.
Now, if you want to achieve your freedom,
you have to learn.
You have to realize that...
you've been doing it backwards.
So...
I'm gonna give you an opportunity...
to turn it all around.
Here's your key to freedom.
It's all up to you.
Now, the game is simple.
The best ones are.
You have one shotgun.
You have one shell.
Like I said, it's up to you.
How can you say Jigsaw isn't dead?
He's dead.
Autopsy was performed on his body.
He has his own grave.
He's not.
Jigsaw lives forever
through the work of his followers.
You.
You've been obsessed
with John Kramer from the start.
The website.
The traps you built.
Lots of people are fascinated by Kramer.
You know damn well
I didn't kill Buckethead.
Or the other two.
Then who did?
Halloran. You said it yourself.
The bullet matches.
He's connected to all the victims.
He's--
Right behind you. Drop it.
Drop it! Both of you.
- Now!
- It's him.
- It's him!
- Go on!
- Don't. Don't.
- Come on.
- Come on!
- All right!
- Don't.
- All right.
All right, I'm putting it down.
Now it's your turn, sweetheart.
Come on, sweetheart.
- No.
- Come on.
Put it down.
I'll blow his fucking brains out.
- El.
- Yeah.
That's a good girl.
All right. You got what you--
Run!
He wants us to shoot each other.
He wants me to kill you.
No.
No. No, don't!
No, don't touch that,
you psycho bitch!
- It's the only way!
- No, no!
No. No. No, okay?
No. No, please don't.
Because that's what he wants us to do.
- Okay? Think about it.
- Thumb on the scale.
No. No, please don't. Okay? Please.
- No, no, no.
- Good or evil.
- No, please don't.
- That's what he said.
Think about this for a minute, okay?
Just think.
We're supposed to follow the rules.
We have to play by the rules.
My only key to freedom...
is to kill you.
Please!
- Please don't! Please don't!
- I'm sorry.
Backwards...
He-- He said we've got it backwards!
No!
Oh, my God,
Oh, my God.
No.
No!
No. No.
Here's your key to freedom.
We could have been free, Anna.
I'm sorry.
Halloran.
Help! Somebody!
Help!
What the fuck are these?
What the fuck?
These are goddamn laser cutters.
What? What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, what happened?
Where's Eleanor?
- Halloran!
- Someone came out of nowhere.
Drugged me. Knocked me out.
Yeah, me too.
Hello, gentlemen.
You came looking for the game.
Congratulations, you found it.
You are the final two players.
It can't be.
You may recognize the device
around your collar, Dr. Nelson.
These laser cutters slice
through tissue and bone like butter.
The most powerful blade on the planet.
You both have an opportunity to live.
All you need to do is confess.
- Confess?
- It's that easy.
If you admit to the reason
that you deserve to die...
you can escape death.
I will be listening.
Make your choice.
How are you alive?
How are you still alive!
The game will select one of you
to begin in 60 seconds.
Unless, of course,
someone chooses to go first.
Let's neither of us touch a button.
We're both gonna be fucked in a minute.
I'll go first.
Okay-
Wait! No, no, no, no!
No! No!
Oh, God!
I've done nothing wrong!
No! Stop! Stop it!
- Stop it!
- I'd confess.
- Yeah.
- Okay, okay, okay! All right!
All right, John Kramer! It was me!
It was me! I fucked up!
I messed up your X-rays!
I was... I was careless.
And I am sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I confess.
Christine, I'm so sorry, baby.
I should have been there for you.
But I wasn't.
Your turn, Detective.
No! No, no, no! I won! I won! I won!
Oh, shit!
- Oh, shit.
- Confess.
Okay-
I did some shitty things.
But the system's broken,
I tried to fix it!
Okay! Okay!
I tampered with evidence.
I-- I took bribes.
I put innocent people away.
Murderers and rapists walked.
People died because of me!
Innocent people died because of me!
I did it!
It fucking can't be.
What?
Hey, hey, hey...
Wha-- What is this?
What are you...
What?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Logan, you're--
What?
What? Hey!
What? You...
You're working with him?
I am him.
What?
And with a little help from you,
no one will ever suspect it.
People died because of me!
Innocent people died because of me.
I did it!
I don't understand.
Ten years ago, in this very barn...
a game was played.
Supposedly, John Kramer designed this
for a game that took place
before all the others.
The bodies were never found.
I know this because
I was one of the players.
Jigsaw put me in that game
almost ten years ago.
I mixed up his X-ray.
You need to cut yourself!
John decided I shouldn't have to die
over an honest mistake.
He gave me a second chance.
So now, ten years later,
I've recreated Jigsaw's game
with criminals from your failed cases.
What?
I wanted my game
to be identical to Jigsaw's.
So I went through your cases.
Found players just like
the ones in the original game.
I gave them the same choices
that Jigsaw did a decade ago.
Jigsaw put five people in his game.
I put in three.
You and I are the last two.
I wanted to see if I was as worthy as him.
As... talented.
No...
Come on, Logan.
Come on. Have mercy.
Like you just had mercy on me?
When you started our game just now?
Pushing my button?
Saving yourself.
What?
That's not fair!
Fair?
Why was Edgar Munsen free?
He was a murderer.
But you were protecting him because
he was your criminal informant years ago.
And you let him walk free.
Edgar Munsen killed my wife.
You don't... You don't know that.
It's never been proven.
This...
won't...
bring your family back.
John Kramer...
gave people a chance to win the game.
A choice.
Fuck! You fucker.
You have a choice.
Scream, or don't.
Logan, Logan, Logan, Logan.
Hey, look, I can help you.
I can-- I can do things for you.
Can you bring my wife back?
Doesn't matter what I say, does it?
I created a game that
appeared to be run by Jigsaw.
Hello, Edgar.
You're about to play a game.
Five lives are in your hands.
Follow my instructions exactly.
I gotta choose who dies, them or me.
I'm not fucking dying.
What kind of firearm do you use?
Glock 22. Most cops do.
Except Halloran, he's got a 17.
Nine by nineteen Parabellum.
That's a Glock 17.
The blood under the fingernails
of our first victim...
is John Kramer's blood.
Some will think it's Jigsaw.
Some will suspect you.
But no one will suspect me.
Okay, we need to bring him in. Now!
Because Eleanor
will provide my alibi.
Oh, yes.
Ten years ago,
I came out of the war a broken man.
Jigsaw put the pieces of my life
back together again.
He gave my life purpose.
We can never come
from anger or from vengeance.
You taught me that.
But then there will be no justice.
Ah, but there Will!
Because we'll speak for the dead.
Together, we built a legacy.
Now, I speak for the lives
ruined by people like you.
Murderers. Rapists.
Their victims appeared
on my table because of you.
No. No.
No...
I speak for the dead.